<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="106">
    <author>TisonK</author>
    <version>1.9.9.9</version>
    <modName>FS25_SoilFertilizer</modName>
    <title>
        <en>Realistic Soil &amp; Fertilizer</en>
        <de>Realistischer Boden &amp; Dünger</de>
        <fr>Sol &amp; Engrais Réalistes</fr>
        <pl>Realistyczna Gleba &amp;Nawóz</pl>
        <es>Suelo &amp; Fertilizante Realistas</es>
        <it>Suolo &amp; Fertilizzante Realistici</it>
        <cz>Realistická Půda &amp; Hnojivo</cz>
        <br>Solo &amp; Fertilizante Realistas</br>
        <uk>Реалістичний грунт та добриво</uk>
        <ru>Реалистичная почва и удобрение</ru>
        <hu>Realisztikus Talaj &amp; Műtrágya</hu>
        <nl>Realistische Bodem &amp; Meststof</nl>
        <ea>Suelo y Fertilizante Realistas</ea>
        <pt>Solo &amp; Fertilizante Realistas</pt>
        <ro>Sol și Îngrășământ Realist</ro>
        <tr>Gerçekçi Toprak &amp; Gübre</tr>
        <fi>Realistinen Maaperä &amp; Lannoite</fi>
        <no>Realistisk Jord &amp; Gjødsel</no>
        <sv>Realistisk Jord &amp; Gödsel</sv>
        <da>Realistisk Jord &amp; Gødning</da>
        <kr>현실적인 토양 및 비료</kr>
        <jp>リアルな土壌と肥料</jp>
        <ct>真實土壤與肥料</ct>
        <fc>真实土壤与肥料</fc>
        <id>Tanah &amp; Pupuk Realistis</id>
        <vi>Đất &amp; Phân Bón Thực Tế</vi>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>Adds realistic per-field soil management to Farming Simulator 25. Tracks Nitrogen, Phosphorus, Potassium, Organic Matter, and pH for every field on the map. Crops deplete nutrients at harvest; fertilizers, manure, and lime replenish them. Rain causes leaching, seasons shift nitrogen levels, and neglected fields slowly recover on their own. Includes a live soil HUD, a full farm soil report (K key), and 9 custom fertilizer types. Fully multiplayer with server-authoritative settings. Works on multifruit maps — unknown crops use a balanced fallback rate. Compatible with Precision Farming: one fertilizer pass updates both mods at the same time — no double work. They track their own independent values (PF per sub-zone, SoilFertilizer per field), so the numbers shown may differ; use PF to see where to apply and this mod to see what to apply.</en>
        <de>Fügt realistisches feldspezifisches Bodenmanagement zu Farming Simulator 25 hinzu. Verfolgt Stickstoff, Phosphor, Kalium, organische Substanz und pH-Wert für jedes Feld. Ernten erschöpfen Nährstoffe; Dünger, Mist und Kalk ergänzen sie. Regen verursacht Auswaschung, Jahreszeiten beeinflussen den Stickstoffgehalt, und brachliegende Felder erholen sich langsam von selbst. Enthält ein Live-Boden-HUD, einen vollständigen Hofbodenbericht (K-Taste) und 9 benutzerdefinierte Düngertypen. Vollständig multiplayer-fähig mit serverautoritativen Einstellungen. Kompatibel mit Precision Farming.</de>
        <fr>Ajoute une gestion réaliste du sol par parcelle à Farming Simulator 25. Suit l'Azote, le Phosphore, le Potassium, la Matière Organique et le pH pour chaque champ. Les récoltes épuisent les nutriments ; les engrais, le fumier et la chaux les reconstituent. La pluie lessive les nutriments, les saisons font varier l'azote, et les champs abandonnés se régénèrent lentement. Comprend un HUD sol en direct, un rapport complet de la ferme (touche K) et 9 types d'engrais personnalisés. Multijoueur complet avec paramètres contrôlés par le serveur. Compatible avec Precision Farming.</fr>
        <pl>Dodaje realistyczne zarządzanie glebą per-pole do Farming Simulator 25. Śledzi Azot, Fosfor, Potas, Materię Organiczną i pH dla każdego pola. Zbiory wyczerpują składniki odżywcze; nawozy, obornik i wapno je uzupełniają. Deszcz powoduje wymywanie, pory roku wpływają na poziom azotu, a zaniedbane pola powoli się regenerują. Zawiera HUD gleby, pełny raport gleby (klawisz K) i 9 niestandardowych typów nawozów. Pełna obsługa trybu wieloosobowego. Kompatybilny z Precision Farming.</pl>
        <es>Añade gestión realista del suelo por campo a Farming Simulator 25. Rastrea Nitrógeno, Fósforo, Potasio, Materia Orgánica y pH para cada campo. Las cosechas agotan los nutrientes; los fertilizantes, el estiércol y la cal los reponen. La lluvia causa lixiviación, las estaciones afectan el nitrógeno, y los campos abandonados se recuperan lentamente. Incluye HUD de suelo en vivo, informe completo de la granja (tecla K) y 9 tipos de fertilizantes personalizados. Multijugador completo con configuración controlada por el servidor. Compatible con Precision Farming.</es>
        <it>Aggiunge una gestione realistica del suolo per campo a Farming Simulator 25. Tiene traccia di Azoto, Fosforo, Potassio, Sostanza Organica e pH per ogni campo. I raccolti esauriscono i nutrienti; fertilizzanti, letame e calce li reintegrano. La pioggia causa lisciviazione, le stagioni influenzano l'azoto e i campi abbandonati si riprendono lentamente. Include HUD del suolo in tempo reale, report completo dell'azienda (tasto K) e 9 tipi di fertilizzanti personalizzati. Multiplayer completo con impostazioni controllate dal server. Compatibile con Precision Farming.</it>
        <cz>Přidává realistickou správu půdy pro každé pole do Farming Simulator 25. Sleduje Dusík, Fosfor, Draslík, Organickou Hmotu a pH pro každé pole. Sklizeň vyčerpává živiny; hnojiva, hnůj a vápno je doplňují. Déšť způsobuje vymývání, roční období ovlivňují dusík a zanedbané pole se pomalu zotavují. Zahrnuje živý HUD půdy, kompletní zprávu o půdě farmy (klávesa K) a 9 vlastních typů hnojiv. Plná podpora pro více hráčů. Kompatibilní s Precision Farming.</cz>
        <br>Adiciona gerenciamento realista de solo por campo ao Farming Simulator 25. Rastreia Nitrogênio, Fósforo, Potássio, Matéria Orgânica e pH para cada campo. As colheitas esgotam os nutrientes; fertilizantes, esterco e calcário os repõem. A chuva causa lixiviação, as estações afetam o nitrogênio e os campos abandonados se recuperam lentamente. Inclui HUD de solo ao vivo, relatório completo da fazenda (tecla K) e 9 tipos de fertilizantes personalizados. Multijogador completo com configurações controladas pelo servidor. Compatível com Precision Farming.</br>
        <uk>Додає реалістичне управління ґрунтом для кожного поля у Farming Simulator 25. Відстежує Азот, Фосфор, Калій, Органічну Речовину та pH для кожного поля. Збір врожаю виснажує поживні речовини; добрива, гній і вапно їх поповнюють. Дощ спричиняє вимивання, сезони впливають на азот, а занедбані поля повільно відновлюються. Включає HUD ґрунту, повний звіт ферми (клавіша K) та 9 типів добрив. Повна підтримка мультиплеєра. Сумісний з Precision Farming.</uk>
        <ru>Добавляет реалистичное управление почвой для каждого поля в Farming Simulator 25. Отслеживает Азот, Фосфор, Калий, Органическое Вещество и pH для каждого поля. Уборка урожая истощает питательные вещества; удобрения, навоз и известь их восполняют. Дождь вызывает вымывание, сезоны влияют на азот, а заброшенные поля медленно восстанавливаются. Включает HUD почвы, полный отчёт фермы (клавиша K) и 9 типов удобрений. Полная поддержка мультиплеера. Совместим с Precision Farming.</ru>
        <hu>Realisztikus talajtani rendszert ad minden mezőhöz a Farming Simulator 25-ben. Követi a Nitrogént, Foszfort, Káliumot, Szerves Anyagot és pH-t minden mezőn. Az aratás tápanyagokat von el; a műtrágyák, trágya és mész pótolják őket. Az eső kilúgozást okoz, az évszakok befolyásolják a nitrogénszintet, az elhanyagolt mezők lassan regenerálódnak. Tartalmaz élő talaj HUD-ot, teljes gazdasági talajjelentést (K gomb) és 9 egyedi műtrágya típust. Teljes többjátékos támogatás. Kompatibilis a Precision Farming-gal.</hu>
        <nl>Voegt realistisch veldspecifiek bodembeheer toe aan Farming Simulator 25. Houdt Stikstof, Fosfor, Kalium, Organische Stof en pH bij voor elk veld. Oogsten putten voedingsstoffen uit; meststoffen, mest en kalk vullen ze aan. Regen veroorzaakt uitspoeling, seizoenen beïnvloeden stikstofniveaus en verwaarloosde velden herstellen langzaam vanzelf. Bevat een live bodem-HUD, een volledig bodemrapport (K-toets) en 9 aangepaste meststoftypen. Volledig multiplayer met server-autoritatieve instellingen. Compatibel met Precision Farming.</nl>
        <ea>Añade gestión realista del suelo por campo a Farming Simulator 25. Rastrea Nitrógeno, Fósforo, Potasio, Materia Orgánica y pH para cada campo. Las cosechas agotan los nutrientes; los fertilizantes, el estiércol y la cal los reponen. La lluvia causa lixiviación, las estaciones afectan el nitrógeno y los campos abandonados se recuperan lentamente. Incluye HUD de suelo en vivo, reporte completo de la granja (tecla K) y 9 tipos de fertilizantes. Multijugador completo. Compatible con Precision Farming.</ea>
        <pt>Adiciona gestão realista de solo por campo ao Farming Simulator 25. Rastreia Azoto, Fósforo, Potássio, Matéria Orgânica e pH para cada campo. As colheitas esgotam os nutrientes; fertilizantes, estrume e calcário repõem-nos. A chuva causa lixiviação, as estações afectam o azoto e os campos abandonados recuperam lentamente. Inclui HUD de solo em tempo real, relatório completo da exploração (tecla K) e 9 tipos de fertilizantes. Multijogador completo. Compatível com Precision Farming.</pt>
        <ro>Adaugă gestionarea realistă a solului per câmp în Farming Simulator 25. Urmărește Azotul, Fosforul, Potasiul, Materia Organică și pH-ul pentru fiecare câmp. Recoltele epuizează nutrienții; îngrășămintele, gunoiul de grajd și varul îi refac. Ploaia cauzează levigare, anotimpurile afectează azotul și câmpurile neglijate se refac lent. Include HUD sol în timp real, raport complet al fermei (tasta K) și 9 tipuri de îngrășăminte. Multiplayer complet. Compatibil cu Precision Farming.</ro>
        <tr>Farming Simulator 25'e tarla başına gerçekçi toprak yönetimi ekler. Haritadaki her tarla için Azot, Fosfor, Potasyum, Organik Madde ve pH'ı takip eder. Hasatlar besinleri tüketir; gübreler, ahır gübresi ve kireç onları yeniler. Yağmur yıkanmaya neden olur, mevsimler azot seviyelerini etkiler ve ihmal edilen tarlalar yavaş yavaş kendiliğinden toparlanır. Canlı toprak HUD'u, tam çiftlik toprak raporu (K tuşu) ve 9 özel gübre türü içerir. Sunucu yetkili ayarlarla tam çok oyunculu. Precision Farming ile uyumlu.</tr>
        <fi>Lisää realistisen peltokohtaisen maaperänhallinnan Farming Simulator 25:een. Seuraa typpeä, fosforia, kaliumia, orgaanista ainesta ja pH:ta jokaisella pellolla. Sadot kuluttavat ravinteita; lannoitteet, lanta ja kalkki palauttavat ne. Sade aiheuttaa ravinteiden huuhtoutumista, vuodenajat vaikuttavat typpitasoihin ja laiminlyödyt pellot toipuvat hitaasti itsekseen. Sisältää reaaliaikaisen maaperä-HUD:n, koko tilan maaperäraaportin (K-näppäin) ja 9 mukautettua lannoitetyyppiä. Täysi moninpeli palvelinohjatuilla asetuksilla. Yhteensopiva Precision Farmingin kanssa.</fi>
        <no>Legger til realistisk jordforvaltning per jorde i Farming Simulator 25. Sporer Nitrogen, Fosfor, Kalium, Organisk Materiale og pH for hvert jorde. Avlinger tapper næringsstoffer; gjødsel, husdyrgjødsel og kalk fyller dem opp igjen. Regn forårsaker utvasking, årstider påvirker nitrogennivåer og forsømte jorder gjenoppretter seg sakte. Inkluderer live jord-HUD, fullstendig gårdsrapport (K-tast) og 9 tilpassede gjødseltyper. Fullt flerspiller med server-autoritative innstillinger. Kompatibel med Precision Farming.</no>
        <sv>Lägger till realistisk markförvaltning per fält i Farming Simulator 25. Spårar Kväve, Fosfor, Kalium, Organiskt Material och pH för varje fält. Skördar förbrukar näringsstoffer; gödsel, stallgödsel och kalk fyller på dem. Regn orsakar urlakning, årstider påverkar kväveniåer och försummade fält återhämtar sig sakta. Inkluderar live mark-HUD, fullständig gårdsrapport (K-tangent) och 9 anpassade gödseltyper. Fullt flerspelsstöd med serverauktoritativa inställningar. Kompatibel med Precision Farming.</sv>
        <da>Tilføjer realistisk markspecifik jordstyring til Farming Simulator 25. Sporer Kvælstof, Fosfor, Kalium, Organisk Materiale og pH for hvert mark. Afgrøder udtømmer næringsstoffer; gødning, husdyrgødning og kalk genopbygger dem. Regn forårsager udvaskning, årstider påvirker kvælstofniveauer og forsømte marker genopretter sig langsomt. Inkluderer live jord-HUD, komplet farmrapport (K-tast) og 9 tilpassede gødningstyper. Fuld multiplayer. Kompatibel med Precision Farming.</da>
        <kr>Farming Simulator 25에 필지별 현실적인 토양 관리를 추가합니다. 지도의 모든 필지에 대해 질소, 인, 칼륨, 유기물 및 pH를 추적합니다. 수확 시 영양소가 소모되며, 비료, 퇴비 및 석회가 이를 보충합니다. 비가 오면 용탈이 발생하고, 계절에 따라 질소 수준이 변하며, 방치된 필지는 서서히 회복됩니다. 실시간 토양 HUD, 전체 농장 토양 보고서(K 키), 9가지 맞춤 비료 타입을 포함합니다. 서버 권한 설정으로 완전한 멀티플레이어 지원. Precision Farming과 호환됩니다.</kr>
        <jp>Farming Simulator 25にフィールドごとのリアルな土壌管理を追加します。マップ上のすべてのフィールドの窒素、リン、カリウム、有機物、pHを追跡します。収穫時に栄養素が消費され、肥料、堆肥、石灰で補充されます。雨による溶脱、季節による窒素レベルの変化、放置されたフィールドの自然回復をシミュレートします。リアルタイム土壌HUD、農場全体の土壌レポート（Kキー）、9種類のカスタム肥料タイプを含みます。サーバー権限設定で完全マルチプレイヤー対応。Precision Farmingと互換性があります。</jp>
        <ct>為 Farming Simulator 25 添加每塊田地的真實土壤管理系統。追蹤地圖上每塊田地的氮、磷、鉀、有機質和 pH 值。收穫時消耗養分；肥料、堆肥和石灰可補充養分。降雨導致養分流失，季節影響氮含量，荒廢的田地會緩慢自然恢復。包含即時土壤 HUD、完整農場土壤報告（K 鍵）和 9 種自訂肥料類型。完整多人遊戲支援。與 Precision Farming 相容。</ct>
        <fc>为 Farming Simulator 25 添加每块田地的真实土壤管理系统。追踪地图上每块田地的氮、磷、钾、有机质和 pH 值。收获时消耗养分；肥料、堆肥和石灰可补充养分。降雨导致养分流失，季节影响氮含量，荒废的田地会缓慢自然恢复。包含实时土壤 HUD、完整农场土壤报告（K 键）和 9 种自定义肥料类型。完整多人游戏支持。与 Precision Farming 兼容。</fc>
        <id>Menambahkan manajemen tanah per-lahan yang realistis ke Farming Simulator 25. Melacak Nitrogen, Fosfor, Kalium, Bahan Organik, dan pH untuk setiap lahan di peta. Panen menguras nutrisi; pupuk, pupuk kandang, dan kapur mengisinya kembali. Hujan menyebabkan pencucian, musim mempengaruhi kadar nitrogen, dan lahan yang diabaikan pulih perlahan. Termasuk HUD tanah langsung, laporan tanah pertanian lengkap (tombol K), dan 9 jenis pupuk khusus. Multiplayer penuh. Kompatibel dengan Precision Farming.</id>
        <vi>Thêm quản lý đất đai thực tế theo từng thửa ruộng vào Farming Simulator 25. Theo dõi Nitơ, Phốt pho, Kali, Chất hữu cơ và pH cho mỗi thửa ruộng trên bản đồ. Thu hoạch làm cạn kiệt dinh dưỡng; phân bón, phân chuồng và vôi bổ sung lại. Mưa gây rửa trôi, mùa vụ ảnh hưởng đến hàm lượng nitơ và những thửa ruộng bị bỏ hoang dần hồi phục. Bao gồm HUD đất trực tiếp, báo cáo đất đầy đủ của trang trại (phím K) và 9 loại phân bón tùy chỉnh. Hỗ trợ đầy đủ nhiều người chơi. Tương thích với Precision Farming.</vi>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
    
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/main.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <actions>
        <action name="SF_TOGGLE_HUD"  category="ONFOOT" />
        <action name="SF_SOIL_REPORT" category="ONFOOT" />
        <action name="SF_RATE_UP"     category="VEHICLE" />
        <action name="SF_RATE_DOWN"   category="VEHICLE" />
        <action name="SF_TOGGLE_AUTO" category="VEHICLE" />
        <action name="SF_CYCLE_MAP_LAYER" category="ONFOOT" />
        <action name="SF_OPEN_SETTINGS"   category="ONFOOT" />
    </actions>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation" />

    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="SF_TOGGLE_HUD">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_J" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="SF_SOIL_REPORT">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_K" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="SF_RATE_UP">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_RIGHTBRACKET" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="SF_RATE_DOWN">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_LEFTBRACKET" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="SF_TOGGLE_AUTO">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_l" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="SF_CYCLE_MAP_LAYER">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_m" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="SF_OPEN_SETTINGS">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_o" />
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>

    <!-- Custom fill types declared in external file (FS25 requires filename= attribute) -->
    <fillTypes filename="fillTypes.xml"/>


    <!--
        ══════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════
        SHOP ITEMS (PALLETS)
        Each entry below registers a purchasable pallet in the in-game shop,
        exactly like base-game fertilizer bags.  Liquid types (UAN32, UAN28,
        ANHYDROUS, STARTER) inherit the liquidFertilizer pallet model.
        Dry/granular types inherit the fertilizer pallet model.
        Players buy a pallet → place it on a field or at a depot →
        fill any compatible sprayer/spreader directly from it.
        ══════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════
    -->
    <storeItems>
        <!-- IBC Liquid Tanks (multi-purchase) -->
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/uan32/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_uan32.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/uan28/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_uan28.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/anhydrous/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_anhydrous.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/starter/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_starter.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquid_urea/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_liquid_urea.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquid_ams/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_liquid_ams.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquid_map/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_liquid_map.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquid_dap/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_liquid_dap.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquid_potash/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_liquid_potash.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/insecticide/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_insecticide.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/fungicide/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_fungicide.xml"/>
        <!-- Big Bags / Solid (multi-purchase) -->
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/urea/multiPurchaseBigBag_urea.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/ams/multiPurchaseBigBag_ams.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/map/multiPurchaseBigBag_map.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/dap/multiPurchaseBigBag_dap.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/potash/multiPurchaseBigBag_potash.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/gypsum/multiPurchaseBigBag_gypsum.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/compost/multiPurchaseBigBag_compost.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/biosolids/multiPurchaseBigBag_biosolids.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/chicken_manure/multiPurchaseBigBag_chicken_manure.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/pelletized_manure/multiPurchaseBigBag_pelletized_manure.xml"/>
        <!-- IBC Liquid Tanks (single) -->
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/uan32/liquidTank_uan32.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/uan28/liquidTank_uan28.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/anhydrous/liquidTank_anhydrous.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/starter/liquidTank_starter.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquid_urea/liquidTank_liquid_urea.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquid_ams/liquidTank_liquid_ams.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquid_map/liquidTank_liquid_map.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquid_dap/liquidTank_liquid_dap.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquid_potash/liquidTank_liquid_potash.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/insecticide/liquidTank_insecticide.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/fungicide/liquidTank_fungicide.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/liquidTank/liquidlime/liquidTank_liquidlime.xml"/>
        <!-- Big Bags / Solid (single) -->
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/urea/bigBag_urea.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/ams/bigBag_ams.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/map/bigBag_map.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/dap/bigBag_dap.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/potash/bigBag_potash.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/gypsum/bigBag_gypsum.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/compost/bigBag_compost.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/biosolids/bigBag_biosolids.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/chicken_manure/bigBag_chicken_manure.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/bigBag/pelletized_manure/bigBag_pelletized_manure.xml"/>
    </storeItems>


    <!-- ═══════════════════════════════════════════════════════════
         HELP LINES  —  ESC > Help > Realistic Soil & Fertilizer
         ═══════════════════════════════════════════════════════════ -->
    <helpLines>

        <!-- ── Category 1: Overview ──────────────────────────── -->
        <category title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_cat_overview">

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_ov_p1_title" iconSliceId="icon_contracts">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_ov_p1_intro_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_ov_p1_intro_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_ov_p1_flow_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_ov_p1_flow_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_ov_p2_title" iconSliceId="icon_contracts">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_ov_p2_rain_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_ov_p2_rain_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_ov_p2_season_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_ov_p2_season_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

        </category>

        <!-- ── Category 2: Getting Started ───────────────────── -->
        <category title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_cat_started">

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p1_title" iconSliceId="icon_contracts">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p1_hud_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p1_hud_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p1_report_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p1_report_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p2_title" iconSliceId="icon_shop">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p2_fert_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p2_fert_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p2_harvest_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p2_harvest_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p3_title" iconSliceId="icon_contracts">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p3_levels_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p3_levels_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p3_access_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_gs_p3_access_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

        </category>

        <!-- ── Category 3: Soil Nutrients ────────────────────── -->
        <category title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_cat_nutrients">

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p1_title" iconSliceId="icon_contracts">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p1_n_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p1_n_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p1_p_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p1_p_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p2_title" iconSliceId="icon_contracts">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p2_k_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p2_k_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p2_ph_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p2_ph_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p3_title" iconSliceId="icon_contracts">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p3_om_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p3_om_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p3_fallow_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p3_fallow_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p4_title" iconSliceId="icon_contracts">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p4_bonus_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p4_bonus_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p4_fatigue_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_nu_p4_fatigue_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

        </category>

        <!-- ── Category 4: Fertilizers ───────────────────────── -->
        <category title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_cat_fertilizers">

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p1_title" iconSliceId="icon_shop">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p1_base_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p1_base_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p1_lime_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p1_lime_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p2_title" iconSliceId="icon_shop">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p2_n_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p2_n_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p2_pk_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p2_pk_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p3_title" iconSliceId="icon_shop">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p3_organic_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p3_organic_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p3_burn_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_fe_p3_burn_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

        </category>

        <!-- ── Category 5: HUD & Soil Report ─────────────────── -->
        <category title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_cat_hud">

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p1_title" iconSliceId="icon_hud_speedometer">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p1_toggle_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p1_toggle_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p1_status_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p1_status_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p2_title" iconSliceId="icon_hud_speedometer">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p2_press_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p2_press_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p2_treat_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p2_treat_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p3_title" iconSliceId="icon_hud_speedometer">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p3_open_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p3_open_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p3_detail_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_hu_p3_detail_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

        </category>

        <!-- ── Category 6: Settings ──────────────────────────── -->
        <category title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_cat_settings">

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_se_p1_title" iconSliceId="icon_contracts">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_se_p1_server_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_se_p1_server_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_se_p1_diff_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_se_p1_diff_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_se_p2_title" iconSliceId="icon_hud_speedometer">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_se_p2_hud_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_se_p2_hud_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_se_p2_rate_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_se_p2_rate_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

        </category>

        <!-- ── Category 7: Multiplayer & PrecisionFarming ────── -->
        <category title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_cat_multiplayer">

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_mp_p1_title" iconSliceId="icon_multiplayer">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_mp_p1_auth_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_mp_p1_auth_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_mp_p1_ded_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_mp_p1_ded_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

            <page title="$l10n_helpLine_sf_mp_p2_title" iconSliceId="icon_multiplayer">
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_mp_p2_compat_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_mp_p2_compat_text"  />
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <title text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_mp_p2_workflow_title" />
                    <text  text="$l10n_helpLine_sf_mp_p2_workflow_text"  />
                </paragraph>
            </page>

        </category>

    </helpLines>

</modDesc>
